Digital Collections and Archives Records UA069
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Digital objects, 1662 -- 2015; 2000 -- 2004; UA069.005; 542 Digital Object(s)
  - The Inevitable Global Conversation, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00236; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "The Inevitable Global Conversation" by Walter B. Wriston for the Winter 1994 edition of the "Media Studies Journal." The original article is located in MS134.003.028.00012.
    Information technology; Libraries; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Incredible Future, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00237; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "Incredible Future" by Walter B. Wriston for the November 1995 edition of "Executive Excellence." The original article is located in MS134.003.028.00015.
    Information technology; International Trade; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Decline of the Central Bankers, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00238; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "The Decline of the Central Bankers" by Walter B. Wriston for the September 20, 1992 edition of "The New York Times." The original article is located in MS134.003.027.00021.
  - A Failure of Management, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00239; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "A Failure of Management" by Walter B. Wriston for the 1995 edition of "Sternbusiness." The original article is located in MS134.003.028.00013.
    Mexico Economic Policy; United States Economic Policy; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Bashing Japan With Flawed Figures, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00240; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "Bashing Japan With Flawed Figures" by Walter B. Wriston for the August 4, 1994 edition of "The Washington Post." The original article is located in MS134.003.028.00011.
    International Trade; Statistics; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Whatever Happened To Walter Wriston? When Walter Wriston was at the helm of Citicorp, the markets and the world paid attention to his every word. Maybe they still should., 2007; UA069.005.DO.00241; King, William B.
    This document was created from the article, "Whatever Happened To Walter Wriston? When Walter Wriston was at the helm of Citicorp, the markets and the world paid attention to his every word. Maybe they still should." by William B. King for the 1993 edition of the "Bank Director." The original article is located in MS134.003.026.00001.
    Interviews; Information technology; Banks and banking; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Advice for the New Mayor, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00242; Stern, William; Cove, Peter; Kotkin, Joel; Savas, E. S.; Biederman, Daniel; McCaughey, Elizabeth; Heinemann, H. Erich; Brooke-Hitching, Harley; Moss, Mitchell; Nathan, Richard; Zuckerman, Mortimer; Cornuelle, Richard; Mahoney, Margaret; Berger, Stephen; Wriston, Walter B.; Morris, Charles; Crouch, Stanley
    This document was created from the article, "Advice for the New Mayor" by Walter B. Wriston, Stanley Crouch, Stephen Berger, Charles Morris, Margaret Mahoney, Richard Cornuelle, Mortimer Zuckerman, Richard Nathan, Mitchell Moss, Harley Brooke-Hitching, H. Erich Heinemann, Elizabeth McCaughey, Daniel Biederman, E. S. Savas, Joel Kotkin, Peter Cove, and William Stern for the Winter 1994 edition of the "City Journal." The original article is located in MS134.003.028.00008.
    New York (N.Y.) Politics and government; Leadership; Wriston, Walter B.; Giuliani, Rudolph W.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty and the Information Standard, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00243; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "The Twilight of Sovereignty and the Information Standard" by Walter B. Wriston for the September/October 1992 edition of "The American Enterprise." The original article is located in MS134.003.027.00022.
  - Technology and Sovereignty, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00244; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "Technology and Sovereignty" by Walter B. Wriston for the Winter 1988/1989 edition of "Foreign Affairs." The original article is located in MS134.003.027.00008.
    Information technology; History; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Microseconds and Macropolicy, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00245; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "Microseconds and Macropolicy" by Walter B. Wriston for the March/April 1985 edition of "Regulation: AEI [American Enterprise Institute] Journal on Government and Society." The original article is located in MS134.003.026.00019.
    Information technology; Technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - To Market, to Market, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00246; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "To Market, to Market" by Walter B. Wriston for the November 7, 1993 edition of "The Washington Post." The original article is located in MS134.003.028.00007.
    Books Reviews; New York Stock Exchange; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00247; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "The Twilight of Sovereignty" by Walter B. Wriston for the November 23, 1992 edition of "The Commonwealth: The Weekly Publication of the Commonwealth Club of California." The original article is located in MS134.003.027.00023.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00248; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "The Twilight of Sovereignty" by Walter B. Wriston for the Summer 1993 edition of the "Fletcher Forum of World Affairs." The original article is located in MS134.003.028.00002.
  - Walter B. Wriston (Response to "Proposal to privatize the World Bank," an article by Nicholas Eberstadt and Clifford M. Lewis), 2007; UA069.005.DO.00249; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "Walter B. Wriston (Response to "Proposal to privatize the World Bank," an article by Nicholas Eberstadt and Clifford M. Lewis)" by Walter B. Wriston for the Summer 1995 edition of "The National Interest." The original article is located in MS134.003.028.00014.
    World Bank; International finance; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Deficit Thinking, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00250; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "Deficit Thinking" by Walter B. Wriston for the July 22, 1993 edition of the "Far Eastern Economic Review." The original article is located in MS134.003.028.00006.
    International Trade; United States Economic Policy; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Walter B. Wriston: Building a Global Financial Services Business Through Communications and Meritocracy, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00251; Davis, Steven I.
    This document was created from the chapter, "Walter B. Wriston: Building a Global Financial Services Business Through Communications and Meritocracy" by Steven I. Davis in his 1997 book, "Leadership in Financial Services: Lessons for the Future." The original chapter is located in MS134.003.025.00019.
    Citicorp; Bank management; Leadership; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Issues, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00252; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "Issues" by Walter B. Wriston for the December 15, 1998 edition of "The Economic Times of New Delhi." The original article is located in MS134.003.029.00005.
    International finance; Banks and banking; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Dumb Networks and Smart Capital, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00253; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "Dumb Networks and Smart Capital" by Walter B. Wriston for the Winter 1998 edition of "The Cato Journal: A Interdisciplinary Journal of Public Policy Analysis." The original article is located in MS134.003.029.00002.
    Information technology; Banks and banking; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Comments on "The Twilight of Sovereignty: How the Information Revolution Is Transforming Our World", 2007; UA069.005.DO.00254; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "Comments on "The Twilight of Sovereignty: How the Information Revolution Is Transforming Our World"" by Walter B. Wriston for the September 16, 1992 edition of "Marketplace" produced by American Public Media. The original article is located in MS134.003.025.00029.
    Information technology; Statistics; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Comments about the Eclectic Society of Phi Nu Theta, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00255; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the speech, "Comments about the Eclectic Society of Phi Nu Theta," written by Walter B. Wriston for Wesleyan University circa 1951. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00001.
    Greek letter societies; Learning and scholarship; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks at the Correspondent Bank Forum, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00256; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks at the Correspondent Bank Forum," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Correspondent Bank Forum on 7 February 1959. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00002.
    International Trade; International finance; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Farrell Ship Launching, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00257; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Farrell Ship Launching," written by Walter B. Wriston for a Farrell Lines' ship launching on 16 February 1963. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00018.
    Merchant marine United States; Shipping finance; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Dollar as a Reserve Currency: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00258; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Dollar as a Reserve Currency: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the 38th Annual Meeting of the Bankers' Association of Foreign Trade on 2 May 1960. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00011.
    Dollar, American; Currency question; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Dollar Today: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00259; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Dollar Today: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the American Chamber of Commerce on 15 September 1961. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00013.
    Dollar, American; Monetary policy United States; Wriston, Walter B.
  - How to Succeed in International Business by Really Trying: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00260; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "How to Succeed in International Business by Really Trying: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the 20th Stanford Business Conference on 14 September 1962. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00015.
    International finance; Industrial management; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Outlook for the Dollar, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00261; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Outlook for the Dollar," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Insurance Forum on 8 November 1962. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00016.
    Dollar, American; Balance of payments United States; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Never Mind the Noise in the Market: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00262; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Never Mind the Noise in the Market: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the First National City Bank's Customers Overseas Conference on 22-24 May 1963. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00021.
    Developing countries Commerce; Capital market; Wriston, Walter B.
  - No Royal Road: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00263; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "No Royal Road: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the 48th Annual Meeting of the National Industrial Conference Board on 21 May 1964. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00022.
    Budget deficits United States; Currency question; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Far--From What? East--of Where?, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00264; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Far--From What? East--of Where?," written by Walter B. Wriston for the 69th Annual Congress of American Industry on 3 December 1964. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00023.
    Investments, American Asia; Asia Commerce; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Balance of Power and the Balance of Payments, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00265
    The document was created from the speech, "The Balance of Power and the Balance of Payments," written by Walter B. Wriston for the U.S. Senate Subcommittee on National Security and International Operations on 13 May 1965. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00025.
    Balance of payments United States; Balance of power; Wriston, Walter B.
  - High Cost of Low Interest, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00266; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "High Cost of Low Interest," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Citibank Insurance Forum on 3 November 1966. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00028.
    Investments, American; Investments, Foreign; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks at the American Assembly Arden House, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00267; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks at the American Assembly Arden House, October 28," written by Walter B. Wriston for the American Assembly Arden House on 28 October 1965. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00026.
    Japan Relations United States; United States Relations Japan; International Trade; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Diplomacy, Ducks and Dollars: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00268; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Diplomacy, Ducks and Dollars: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the World Affairs Council of Pittsburgh on 10 May 1966. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00027.
    United States Economic Policy; Trade regulations; Wriston, Walter B.
  - You Can't Get There From Here: An Urban Proposal, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00269; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "You Can't Get There From Here: An Urban Proposal," written by Walter B. Wriston for the New York Commerce and Industry Association on 25 October 1967. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00032.
    Urban renewal New York (State) New York; Urban policy New York (State) New York; Wriston, Walter B.
  - How do You What?: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00270; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "How do You What?: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the First National City Bank Correspondent Bank Forum on 3 February 1968. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00033.
    Bank management; Organizational change; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The New Servitude: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00271; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The New Servitude: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Corporate Management Conference on 23 April 1968. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00001.
    United States Economic Policy; Capital market; Wriston, Walter B.
  - A Long View of the Short Run: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00272; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "A Long View of the Short Run: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the International Chamber of Commerce on 24 October 1968. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00002.
    United States--Foreign relations; Presidents--United States; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Those Were the Days, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00273; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Those Were the Days," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Correspondent Bank Forum on 8 February 1969. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00004.
  - Bank Credit Policies - In the Environment of Tomorrow, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00274; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Bank Credit Policies - In the Environment of Tomorrow," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Reserve City Bankers Association Meeting on 1 April 1969. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00005.
    United States Economic Policy; Bank credit; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Riskless Society Reexamined: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00275; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Riskless Society Reexamined: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the First National City Bank's first combined Board and Trust Board meeting outside the American Continent on 28 May 1969. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00006.
    Technology; Banks and banking; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Values and Obligations of Leadership, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00276; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Values and Obligations of Leadership," written by Walter B. Wriston for a First National City Bank Board meeting during the 1970s. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00007.
    Leadership; Bank management; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Nothing Fails Like Success: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00277; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Nothing Fails Like Success: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the First National City Bank Correspondent Bank Forum on 7 February 1970. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00008.
  - Testimony given at the U.S. Senate Banking & Currency Committee, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00278; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Testimony given at the U.S. Senate Banking & Currency Committee," written by Walter B. Wriston for the U.S. Senate Banking & Currency Committee on 26 May 1970. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00010.
    Bank holding companies United States; Banking law United States; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Testimony of Walter B. Wriston before the Ways and Means Committee of the House of Representative, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00279; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Testimony of Walter B. Wriston before the Ways and Means Committee of the House of Representative," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Ways and Means Committee of the House of Representative on 13 September 1967. The original speech is located in MS134.001.001.00031.
    Taxation United States; Banking law United States; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The New 'ISM': An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00280; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The New 'ISM': An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the American Club on 22 February 1971. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00011.
    International economic relations; Free Trade; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Currency of Change, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00281; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Currency of Change," written by Walter B. Wriston for Citicorp/Citibank Combined Boards Meeting on 28 October 1971. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00014.
    International Trade; Trade regulations; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Modern Pharisee: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00282; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Modern Pharisee: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Religion in American Life Dinner on 7 March 1972. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00015.
    Pharisees; Public Interest; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Global Attic: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00283; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Global Attic: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Bankers' Association for Foreign Trade on 9 May 1972. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00016.
    Dollar, American; International finance; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Dissent of the Majority, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00284; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Dissent of the Majority," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Regional Plan Association on 5 April 1973. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00020.
    Urban policy New York (State) New York; Urban renewal New York (State) New York; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks for the Annual Meeting of Economic Development Council, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00285; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks for the Annual Meeting of Economic Development Council," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Annual Meeting of Economic Development Council on 22 May 1973. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00021.
    Public schools New York (State) New York; Education New York (State) New York; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Capital Formation What is the Question, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00286; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Capital Formation What is the Question," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Business Council on 12 October 1974. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00029.
    Capital investments; Inflation (Finance) United States; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The World Economy: Dr. Pangloss vs. Jeremiah, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00287; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The World Economy: Dr. Pangloss vs. Jeremiah," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Institute of Directors on 25 October 1974. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00031.
    United States Economic Policy; Inflation (Finance) United States; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Blue Eagles and Deja Vu, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00288; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Blue Eagles and Deja Vu," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Society of American Business Writers on 5 May 1975. The original speech is located in MS134.001.002.00034.
  - Newton's Law and Homing Instinct or The Fish are Eating Too Much, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00289; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Newton's Law and Homing Instinct or The Fish are Eating Too Much," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Society of American Business Writers on 5 May 1975. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00001.
  - Remarks at the Topping Out Ceremony, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00290; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks at the Topping Out Ceremony," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Topping Out Ceremony at Citicorp Center on 6 October 1976. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00010.
    Citicorp; Banks and banking; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks at the Citicorp Cornerstone Ceremony, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00291; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks at the Citicorp Cornerstone Ceremony," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Citicorp Cornerstone Ceremony on 31 October 1976. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00011.
  - Remarks by Walter B. Wriston, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00292; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks by Walter B. Wriston," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Regional Senof Conference on 21-24 July 1975. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00002.
    Citicorp; Bank management; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Liberty, Leadership and License, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00293; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Liberty, Leadership and License," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Management Conference at the University of Chicago Graduate School of Business on 11 March 1976. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00006.
    Leadership; Mass media; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Report on Reorganization, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00294; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Report on Reorganization," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Economic Development Council Luncheon on 7 April 1976. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00007.
    New York (N.Y.) Politics and government; Economics.; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Accounting To Whom For What?, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00295; Wriston, Walter B.